<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ben Overmyer</title>
    <link>https://benovermyer.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ben Overmyer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 18:09:03 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://benovermyer.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Résumé</title>
      <link>https://benovermyer.com/page/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 18:09:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benovermyer.com/page/resume/</guid>
      <description>The chief aim of any web technologist is to make a particular part of the web more awesome for people. Or at least, it should be. The web was built for people. For my part, I now manage a team of engineers responsible for building out performant and highly-available digital infrastructure. My history as an engineer in the same capacity and my particular talents for guiding others and seeing the big picture have led me down this path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Published Works</title>
      <link>https://benovermyer.com/page/published-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 09:09:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benovermyer.com/page/published-works/</guid>
      <description>Over the years I’ve released a variety of books, articles, and other documents into the wild. Some of these were published in the true print sense, and some were only released online.
These are listed in reverse chronological order. Where possible, I included a link to the most recent publicly available version.
Books Writer Credit  Master Nicholas and the Wayward Wizardry (Silver Gryphon Games, 2013)
 A Darkness at Summerfort (Silver Gryphon Games, 2013)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://benovermyer.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 08:46:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benovermyer.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Professional Background I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer who loves the web. Not just web technology, mind you; the very idea of the web. Since its inception, it has changed the world. It&amp;rsquo;s my job and my passion to make it better.
I have travelled the world, lived abroad, and usually only ever lived in one place for a couple years. That changed when I moved to Minneapolis. Of all the places I&amp;rsquo;ve lived on this globe, Minneapolis has been my favorite.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>