<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ben Overmyer</title>
    <link>https://benovermyer.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ben Overmyer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 18:09:03 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://benovermyer.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Résumé</title>
      <link>https://benovermyer.com/page/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 18:09:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benovermyer.com/page/resume/</guid>
      <description>The chief aim of any web technologist is to make a particular part of the web more awesome for people. Or at least, it should be. The web was built for people. For my part, I now manage a team of engineers responsible for building out performant and highly-available digital infrastructure. My history as an engineer in the same capacity and my particular talents for guiding others and seeing the big picture have led me down this path, and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be happier about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Published Works</title>
      <link>https://benovermyer.com/page/published-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 09:09:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benovermyer.com/page/published-works/</guid>
      <description>Over the years I’ve released a variety of books, articles, and other documents into the wild. Some of these were published in the true print sense, and some were only released online.
These are listed in reverse chronological order. Where possible, I included a link to the most recent publicly available version. I’ve only listed those works where I was the sole or primary author.
Books  Master Nicholas and the Wayward Wizardry (Silver Gryphon Games, 2013)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://benovermyer.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 08:46:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benovermyer.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Regarding this Page About pages by definition are very self-centered. Their whole purpose is to let the author talk about him/herself. Given that, I am not going to pull any punches or be diplomatic in my declarations. No apologies. I&amp;rsquo;m not trying to sell myself here; I&amp;rsquo;m trying to give you an idea of who I am.
Professional Background I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer who loves the web. Not just web technology, mind you; the very idea of the web.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>